Guide to the Office of Student Activities and Facilities Records, 1936-ongoing UA.09.05.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA 2005-0068, circa 1970-2003, 150 folders
  - Various files--events, Duke Union, and Major Attractions, 1970-2005, 18 folders
    - DUU Performing Arts--The Nutcracker, 1970 (Box 27)
    - DUU Performing Arts--The Book of Job, 1970-1971 (Box 27)
    - Duke Video Yearlooks--miscellaneous correspondence, contracts, and records, 1983-1998 (Box 27)
    - Duke Video Yearlooks--rights and permission statements, 1990-1998 (Box 27)
    - Experience Music Project--Electric Bus, 2001 (Box 27)
    - Last Day of Classes (LDOC), 1997-2003, 3 folders (Box 27)
    - Major Attractions--DMCB, 2001 (Box 27)
    - John Mayer, 2002 (Box 27)
    - Sample contracts, 2001 (Box 27)
    - Schedules, 1978-1979 (Box 27)
    - University Union Board (UUB)--proposals, 1997-2001 (Box 27)
- Accession UA 2006-0010, circa 1990-1999, 6 boxes
  OSAF records include student organization information files, as well as program records of the Craft Center (Box UA2006-10.5). Student organization information files are filed alphabetically.
  - ACLU (American Civil Liberties Union), 1993-2001 (Box 27)
  - Adopt a Grandparent, 2001 (Box 27)
  - African Students Association, 1994-1999 (Box 27)
  - AHA (Anti-Hunger Alliance), 1999-2001 (Box 27)
  - Air Force Reserve Officer Training Corps, 1999 (Box 27)
  - AISEC (International Association of Students in Economy and Commerce), 1980-1996 (Box 27)
  - Alpha Epsilon Phi, 1996-1997 (Box 27)
  - Alpha Kappa Alpha, 1984-1994 (Box 27)
  - Alpha Phi Omega, 1980-2000, 2 folders (Box 27)
  - American Society of Civil Engineers--charter file, 1974-1995 (Box 27)
  - American Society of Mechanical Engineers--charter file, 1976-1995 (Box 27)
  - Amnesty International--budget, charter, and correspondence/roster files, 1982-2000 (Box 27)
  - Arnold Air Society, 1986-1998 (Box 27)
  - Art and Art History Majors' Union, 1994-1996 (Box 27)
  - Associated Students of Duke University (ASDU)1979-1995, 8 folders
    - budget, 1979-1995, 2 folders (Box 27)
    - check cashing and recognized clubs, 1980-1995 (Box 27)
    - correspondence file, 1979-1995 (Box 28)
    - ASDU/DSG budget, 1992-1993 (Box 28)
    - Legislature, 1991-1994; 2 folders (Box 28)
    - line-item budget, 1989-1992 (Box 28)
  - Ashanti, 1995-1996 (Box 28)
  - Asian Student Association, 1981-2000 (Box 28)
  - ASO (Arab Student Organization), 1998-2000 (Box 28)
  - Baptist Student Union, 1988-1995 (Box 28)
  - Bench and Bar Society, 1974-1999 (Box 28)
  - Best Buddies, 1989-2000 (Box 28)
  - A Better Chance Alumni Network, 1995 (Box 28)
  - Biological Anthropology and Anatomy Majors' Union, 1999-2000 (Box 28)
  - Biological Sciences Majors' Union, 1980-1992 (Box 28)
  - Biology Majors' Union, 1993-2000 (Box 28)
  - Biomedical Engineering Society--charter file, 1976-1992 (Box 28)
  - Black Campus Ministries, 1979-1996 (Box 28)
  - Black Women's Collective, 1997-1999 (Box 28)
  - Blind Spot (Journal of Speculative Fiction), 1994-1995 (Box 28)
  - Break for a Change, 1994-2000 (Box 28)
  - The Brown and Green Theater, 1997-1999 (Box 28)
  - Black Students Alliance (BSA)--correspondence, 1980-2000 (Box 28)
  - BSA--Dance Black, 1972-1995 (Box 28)
  - BSA--miscellaneous, 1978-1995 (Box 28)
  - Business Endeavors Association, 1984-1995 (Box 28)
  - Cambridge Christian Fellowship, 1994-2000 (Box 28)
  - Campus Crusade for Christ--charter and correspondence files, 1984-1996 (Box 28)
  - Campus Ministry, 1985-1993 (Box 28)
  - Campus Social Board, 1997-1998 (Box 28)
  - CAPA (Black Pre-Law Society), 1994 (Box 28)
  - Catholic Student Center, 1987-1998 (Box 28)
  - CAUSA (Cuban-American Undergraduate Student Association), 1999 (Box 28)
  - Central American Solidarity Committee, 1981-1991 (Box 28)
  - CHANCE (Concern and Help for the Advancement of Needy Children through Education), 1985-2000 (Box 28)
  - The Chanticleer, 1981-1991 (Box 28)
  - Chess Club, 1981-2000 (Box 28)
  - Child Enrichment Program, 1992-1993 (Box 28)
  - Chinese Folk Dance Club, 1990-2000 (Box 28)
  - Chinese Student and Scholar Association, 1996 (Box 28)
  - Chishin Ryu Karate Club, 1995 (Box 28)
  - The Chosen Generation, 1992-1993 (Box 28)
  - Christian Science Organization, 1987-1996 (Box 28)
  - Circle K--charter file, 1973-1999 (Box 28)
  - Class of 1994-2000, 1991-1999 (Box 28)
  - CLC Coffee Fund, 1998 (Box 28)
  - Coffeehouse, 1981-2001 (Box 28)
  - College Bowl, 1981-2000 (Box 28)
  - College Republicans--charter file, 1979-2000 (Box 29)
  - The Commons, 1998-1999 (Box 29)
  - Community Health Alliance, 1993-1994 (Box 29)
  - Community Service Center, 1993-2000 (Box 29)
  - Comparative Area Studies Majors' Union--charter file, 1984-1995 (Box 29)
  - Conference on Career Choices, 1993-1996 (Box 29)
  - Council of Freshmen Presidents, 1982-1994 (Box 29)
  - Crafts Project, 1994-1995 (Box 29)
  - Delta Delta Delta, 1990-1994 (Box 29)
  - Delta Phi Alpha, 1984-1996 (Box 29)
  - Desegregate Duke, 1997 (Box 29)
  - Dignity, 1993-1994 (Box 29)
  - DIRA (Duke International Relations Association), 1996-1998 (Box 29)
  - Divinity Student Representative Association, 1996 (Box 29)
  - DIYA (South Asian-American Association of Duke), 1995-2000 (Box 29)
  - Domino, 1994 (Box 29)
  - DRAGO (Duke Gaming Society), 1988-1999 (Box 29)
  - Duke Student Government (DSG), 1992-1995 (Box 29)
  - Undergraduate Distinguished Speakers (Box 29)
  - DukeAnime, 1999-2000 (Box 29)
  - Duke Arts Club, 1995 (Box 29)
  - Duke Baha'i Club, 1986-1994 (Box 29)
  - Duke Ballroom Dance Club, 1997-2000 (Box 29)
  - Duke Black Pre-Health Organization, 1997-2000 (Box 29)
  - Duke Business Club, 1994-2000 (Box 29)
  - Duke Campus Band Coalition, 1998 (Box 29)
  - Duke Cancer Patient Support Program, 1993 (Box 29)
  - Duke Child Abuse Prevention Program, 1997 (Box 29)
  - DCOYS (Duke Coalition of Youth Services), 1997 (Box 29)
  - Duke Constitutional Law Project, 1992-1993 (Box 29)
  - Duke Cricket Club, 1998-2000 (Box 29)
  - Duke Dance Club, 1980-1996 (Box 29)
  - Duke Democrats, 1985-2000 (Box 29)
  - Duke-Durham Partners, 1997-1999 (Box 29)
  - Duke Education Task Force, 1992-1994 (Box 29)
  - Duke Entrepreneur Club, 1998 (Box 29)
  - DukeFund, 1993-1994 (Box 29)
  - Duke Gleaning Network, 1992-1995 (Box 29)
  - Duke Harmony Association, 1990-1994 (Box 29)
  - Duke Hellenic Association, 1998-2000 (Box 29)
  - Duke Hillel, 1985-2000 (Box 29)
  - Duke Hunger and Homeless Coalition, 1991-1993 (Box 29)
  - Duke India Association, 1985-1995 (Box 29)
  - Duke INROADers, 2000 (Box 29)
  - Duke Islamic Community, undated (Box 29)
  - Duke Israel Public Affairs Committee, 1980-1993 (Box 29)
  - Duke Juggling Club, 1999-2000 (Box 29)
  - The Duke Meditation Group, 1997 (Box 29)
  - The Duke Mind, 2000 (Box 29)
  - Duke Minority Business Association, 2000 (Box 29)
  - Duke Mock Trial Team, 1993-2001 (Box 29)
  - Duke NAACP, 1994-2000 (Box 29)
  - Duke New Asian Strings Ensemble, 1995 (Box 29)
  - Duke Objectivists, 1998-2001 (Box 29)
  - Duke Outing Club, 1970-1997 (Box 29)
  - Duke Pals, 1992-2000 (Box 29)
  - Duke Philosophical Society, 1998-1999 (Box 29)
  - Duke Political Science Club, 1998-2000 (Box 29)
  - Duke Robotics Club, 1999-2001 (Box 29)
  - Duke SOS (Student Online Support), 1999-2000 (Box 29)
  - Duke Students for George Bush for President, 1993-200 (Box 29)
  - Duke Undergraduate Chemical Society, 1994-1997 (Box 29)
  - Duke University Drum Line, 1994-1995 (Box 29)
  - Duke University Improv, 1997-1999 (Box 29)
  - Duke University Rescue Squad, 1994-2000 (Box 29)
  - Duke University Undergraduate Publications Board, 1983-2001 (Box 29)
  - Duke Wind Symphony, 1977-1999 (Box 29)
  - Duke Women of Color United, 1995-2000 (Box 29)
  - DUMB, 1991-1994 (Box 29)
  - Durham Community Interns, 1993-1994 (Box 29)
  - Durham Direction, 1998-2000 (Box 29)
  - Durham Education Volunteers (formerly Duke Student Tutors), 1982-1995 (Box 29)
  - Earning by Learning, 1995-1996 (Box 29)
  - ECOS (Environmentally Concerned Organization of Students), 1976-1996 (Box 29)
  - Edgemont Afterschool Tutoring Program, 1993-1994 (Box 29)
  - ELIMU (Durham Housing Authority Tutoring Program), 1990-1997 (Box 29)
  - ESL for Marketplace Workers, 1999-2000 (Box 29)
  - Engineering Student Government--correspondence, 1976-1995 (Box 29)
  - English Majors' Union, 1978-1993 (Box 29)
  - Environmental Alliance, 1991-2001 (Box 29)
  - Environmental Science Policy Majors' Union, 1992-1993 (Box 29)
  - Episcopal Student Fellowship, 1997-2000 (Box 29)
  - Eruditio, 1996-1997 (Box 29)
  - ESTEEM (Educational Support to Eliminate Eating Misconceptions), 1993 (Box 29)
  - Ethics Initiative, 1996 (Box 29)
  - FAC (Freshmen Advisory Counselor) Steering Committee--correspondence, 1980-1996 (Box 29)
  - Fellowship of Christian Athletes--charter file, 1982-1993 (Box 29)
  - Feminist Majority Leadership Alliance and FeM, 1994-2000 (Box 29)
  - Forplay Theater, 1997-2001 (Box 29)
  - Fresco Audio Productions, 1992-1993 (Box 29)
  - Friends of TROSA--adult tutoring, 1998-2000 (Box 29)
  - Future Is Now, 1993-2000 (Box 29)
  - Get Away, 1993-1996 (Box 29)
  - Gilbert-Addoms Housing Council, 1993-1994 (Box 29)
  - Global Nomads, 1993-1999 (Box 29)
  - Golden Key National Honor Society, 1987-1996 (Box 29)
  - Gothic Queers (formerly Duke Gay/Bisexual/Lesbian Association), 1986-2000 (Box 29)
  - GPSC (Graduate and Professional Students Council), 1984-1995 (Box 29)
  - Graduate Gay and Lesbian Alliance, 1988-1993 (Box 29)
  - Green Earth Gang and Green House, 1991-1994 (Box 29)
  - Grüv Productions, 1999-2001 (Box 29)
  - Habitat for Humanity, 1988-2001 (Box 29)
  - Hanes House--audit, 1992-1993 (Box 29)
  - Headstart, 1993-1999 (Box 29)
  - Hindu Students Council, 1998-2001 (Box 29)
  - Hoof 'n' Horn, 1982-2001 (Box 29)
  - Household of Deofol Bael (Society for Creative Anachronism), 1990-1992 (Box 29)
  - Imago Dei, 1998-2001 (Box 29)
  - Independent Student Association, 1995-1996 (Box 29)
  - Intercultural Affairs Director, 1992-1993 (Box 29)
  - Interfraternity Council, 1978-1995 (Box 29)
  - International Association, 1984-2001 (Box 29)
  - Intervarsity Christian Fellowship, 1985-2001 (Box 29)
  - International Relations Association (Box 29)
  - Japan-America Club, 1986-1994 (Box 29)
  - Jewish Learning Experience and Jewish Political Action Network, 1995-1997 (Box 29)
  - Juggling Club, 1985-1996 (Box 29)
  - Kangaroo Productions, 1993-1994 (Box 29)
  - Kazi Ya Sanoa (Work of Art), 1995-1997 (Box 29)
  - Kickboxing Club, 1999-2000 (Box 29)
  - Koinonia, 1988-1993 (Box 29)
  - Kokondo Academy, 1995-1996 (Box 29)
  - Korean Christian Fellowship, 1997-1998 (Box 29)
  - Korean Student and Scholars Association, 1996 (Box 29)
  - LAA (LEAD Alumni Association), 1999-2000 (Box 29)
  - Lady Blue, 1991-1997 (Box 30)
  - LAFO (Learning a Lot From Others), 1994-2001 (Box 30)
  - Latino Life Connection, 1999-2000 (Box 30)
  - Latter-Day Saints Student Association, 1987-2001 (Box 30)
  - LEAPS, 1995-2001 (Box 30)
  - Literature and Cultural Studies Society, 1998-2000 (Box 30)
  - Lutheran Campus Ministry, 1985-1996 (Box 30)
  - Lystra Music, 1985-1998 (Box 30)
  - Maxwell House Living Group, 1993-1994 (Box 30)
  - The McDonald Group (McKids), 1994-2000 (Box 30)
  - Mi Gente, 1992-2001 (Box 30)
  - Mind-Body Group, 1993-1995 (Box 30)
  - Model United Nations Club, 1982-1996 (Box 30)
  - Momentum, 1997-2000 (Box 30)
  - Morehead Science Volunteers, 1993-2000 (Box 30)
  - Museo, 1997-1998 (Box 30)
  - Muslim Students Association, 1988-2000 (Box 30)
  - NAJD-The Arabic Language Club, 1994-2001 (Box 30)
  - National Journal of Young Investigators, 1997 (Box 30)
  - National Society of Collegiate Scholars, 1999-2000 (Box 30)
  - Native American Student Coalition, 1992-2001 (Box 30)
  - Naval Historians, 1991-1999 (Box 30)
  - Navigators (Chapel Offices), 1985-2000 (Box 30)
  - NC Student Rural Health Coalition--charter file, 1979-2000 (Box 30)
  - No Boundaries, 1989-200 (Box 30)
  - Odyssey of the Mind, 1994-1995 (Box 30)
  - Officer's Christian Fellowship, 1994-1997 (Box 30)
  - Omicron Delta Epsilon, 1997-1998 (Box 30)
  - Operation Smile, 1997-2000 (Box 30)
  - Out of the Blue, 198-1996 (Box 30)
  - Pakistani Student Club, 1999-2000 (Box 30)
  - Panhellenic Council, 1982-1999 (Box 30)
  - Partnership for Literacy, 1993-2001 (Box 30)
  - Peer Mentoring Program, 1999-2000 (Box 30)
  - Phi Eta Sigma, 1981-1994 (Box 30)
  - Philosophy Nite, 1994 (Box 30)
  - Phi Sigma Pi, 1998-1999 (Box 30)
  - PICAD (Peer Information and Counseling on Alcohol and Drugs), 1987-1994 (Box 30)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha, 1995-1996 (Box 30)
  - The Pitchforks, 1980-1996 (Box 30)
  - Pixel-Eyze Productions, 1999-2000 (Box 30)
  - Plan V (Vegetarian Club), 1988-2001 (Box 30)
  - Society of Pre-Medical Students (Box 30)
  - Presbyterian Fellowship, 1988-1996 (Box 30)
  - Project BUILD (Building Undergraduate Involvement in Life in Durham), 1989-1994 (Box 30)
  - Project Wild and Project Wild Rope Course, 197-2001 (Box 30)
  - Psi Upsilon, 1984-1994 (Box 30)
  - Psychology Majors' Union, 1997-2000 (Box 30)
  - Public Policy Majors' Union, 1976-1999 (Box 30)
  - Rainforest Action Group, 1989-1994 (Box 30)
  - Raptures Christian Fellowship, 1988-1994 (Box 30)
  - Rhythm and Blue, 1993-1999 (Box 30)
  - Rough Riders Snowboarding Club, 1998-1999 (Box 30)
  - Russian Club, 1981-1999 (Box 30)
  - SA Fee, 1987-1993 (Box 30)
  - Safewalks/Saferides, 1986-1994 (Box 30)
  - SALAP, 1991-1993, 2 folders (Box 30)
  - Science Explorers, 1993-1994 (Box 30)
  - Self-Knowledge Symposium, 1994-2000 (Box 30)
  - SEAC (Student Environmental Action Coalition), 1993-1994 (Box 30)
  - SETA (Students for the Ethical Treatment of Animals), 1986-2000 (Box 30)
  - SHARE Living Group, 1997-1998 (Box 30)
  - SHC (Student Health Coalition), 1995 (Box 30)
  - SHRA (Student Humanitarian Relief Association), 1997-1999 (Box 30)
  - SMaRT (Science and Math Achiever Team), 1997-2000 (Box 30)
  - Society of Automotive Engineers, 1991-1994 (Box 30)
  - Society of Black Engineers, 1996-1997 (Box 30)
  - Society of Pre-Medical Students, 1992-2000 (Box 30)
  - Society of Women Engineers--charter file, 1980-1999 (Box 30)
  - Solar Electric Automotive Society, 1992-1993 (Box 30)
  - Something Borrowed, Something Blue, 1998-2001 (Box 30)
  - Sophomore Class Council, 1998-1999 (Box 30)
  - Speak of the Devil, 1991-1996 (Box 30)
  - Spectrum Coalition, 1989-2001 (Box 30)
  - STEP (Student Action to End Poverty), 1999-2000 (Box 30)
  - Sports Clubs, 1984-2000 (Box 30)
  - Steppin' Up, 1998-2000 (Box 30)
  - Student Action with Farmworkers, 1998-2000 (Box 30)
  - Student Activist Cooperative, 1987-1993 (Box 30)
  - Students Against Multiple Sclerosis, 1987-1993 (Box 30)
  - Students Against Sweatshops, 1997-2001 (Box 30)
  - Student Art Volunteers, 1990-1998 (Box 30)
  - Students for a Free Tibet, 1998-2000 (Box 30)
  - Students for America, 1988-1996 (Box 30)
  - Students for Choice, 1988-1993 (Box 30)
  - Students for Life, 1980-2001 (Box 30)
  - Students for Service Learning, 1994-1995 (Box 30)
  - Students of the Caribbean, 1991-2000 (Box 30)
  - Student Religious Activities, 1994-1996 (Box 30)
  - Student Organizations--insurance, 1980-1993 (Box 30)
  - Students to Unite Duke, 1998-2001 (Box 30)
  - SWING Magazine, 1990-1994 (Box 30)
  - Teach for America, 1989-1994 (Box 30)
  - Technical Consulting and Duke Support, 1994-1996 (Box 30)
  - Tobacco Road, 1978-1993 (Box 30)
  - Toys and Tales, 1998-2000 (Box 30)
  - Turkish Student Association, 1995-1999 (Box 30)
  - Union, 1972-1993, 2 folders (Box 30)
  - United Jewish Appeal, 1992-1997 (Box 31)
  - United Way, 1993-1997 (Box 31)
  - Upperclass Housing Association, 1993-1995 (Box 31)
  - Vertices, 1983-1996 (Box 31)
  - Volunteers for Youth, 1981-1996 (Box 31)
  - Wannamaker Reunion, 1995-1996 (Box 31)
  - Wayne Manor, 1998-1999 (Box 31)
  - The Wendell Theater Group, 1991-2001 (Box 31)
  - Wesley Fellowship, 1985-2001 (Box 31)
  - West End Child Enrichment Program, 1992-1994 (Box 31)
  - Women's Coalition, 1989-1996 (Box 31)
  - Women's Health Peer Educator, 1993-1994 (Box 31)
  - WOODS (Wilderness Outdoors Opportunities for Durham Students), 1986-2001 (Box 31)
  - Youth Outreach, 1981-1994 (Box 31)
  - Craft Center, 1975-2001, 25 folders
    - Annual report, 1993-1994 (Box 31)
    - Semester Reports, 1996-1999 (Box 31)
    - Spring report, 1994 (Box 31)
    - Southgate Craft Center blueprints, 1975 (Box 31)
    - Collaborative projects--pottery, 2000 (Box 31)
    - Planning, 1997-1999 (Box 31)
    - Advertising and donations, 1999-2000 (Box 31)
    - Brochures, 1994-2001 (Box 31)
    - Photos, undated (Box 31)
    - West Campus Union blueprints, 1993 (Box 31)
    - NC Pottery Center, 1995-2000 (Box 31)
    - Continuing Education, 1989-1994 (Box 31)
    - class planning sheets, 1998-2000, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - East Campus Craft Center, 1973-1981 (Box 31)
    - University Center blueprints, undated (Box 31)
    - new position, 1996 (Box 31)
    - Empty Bowls--response surveys, 1991-1992 (Box 31)
    - Empty Bowls--media material, 1991-1992 (Box 31)
    - Opinion letters, 1997-1999 (Box 31)
    - Bryan Center--proposal and task force, 1992-1994 (Box 31)
    - Building floor plans, 1995 (Box 31)
    - Craft Center Statistics (Box 31)
    - West C2 blueprints, 1978 (Box 32)
    - East Campus Renovation blueprints, 1983-1988 (Box 32)
  - Cable 13--budget and van, 1992-1993 (Box 31)
  - Facilities Management, 1994-1996 (Box 31)
- Accession UA 2006-0045, 1959-2006, 13 boxes
  Records include materials related to Duke Student Government, the Duke University Union, ongoing campus series such as Major Attractions and Major Speakers, the Office of University Life, and extensive event registration forms and contracts related to the Events Advising Committee (EAC).
  Arrangement: Materials were received predominantly unarranged, with some folders batched by campus group, some chronologically, and some in no discernible order. Arrangement is now chronological by fiscal year. Fiscal years 1959-1994, which contain only a small amount of material, are arranged in one group by folder title. Following that, FY 1994-95 through FY 2005-06 are arranged year-by-year, and will be made available to researchers as each successive 25-year restriction is lifted.
  - Fiscal years 1959-1994 (Box 33)
    - ASDU--historical documents, 1969-1980 (Box 33)
    - Bryan Center policy manuals, 1982-1982, 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Building contact items, 1993 (Box 33)
    - Cable 13 development, 1989 (Box 33)
    - Camarda, Geri, 1989 (Box 33)
    - Coolidge, Caroline, 1989 (Box 33)
    - DSG budget, 1993-1994 (Box 33)
    - Dress code policy, 1986 (Box 33)
    - Duke News Service, 1982 (Box 33)
    - Duke University Union (DUU), 1964-1994; 19 folders
      - Advertising chairman, 1977-1985 (Box 33)
      - Capital assets, 1992 (Box 33)
      - Committee reports, 1988-1989 (Box 33)
      - Coordinator, 1994 (Box 33)
      - Endowed funds, 1989 (Box 33)
      - Events, 1987-1988 (Box 33)
      - Fall reports, 1991-1992 (Box 33)
      - Financial, 1993 (Box 33)
      - Fine Arts Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 33)
      - Graduate Student Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 33)
      - Holiday treelighting, 1984 (Box 33)
      - Meetings, 1990 (Box 33)
      - Newsletters, 1988-1989 (Box 33)
      - Philosophy, 1975 (Box 33)
      - Program Enhancement Fund Policy, 1991-1992 (Box 33)
      - Program reports, 1989-1994; 2 folders (Box 33)
      - Purpose and policies, 1990-1992 (Box 33)
      - Semester reports, 1990-1991 (Box 33)
    - Finance, short-term investments, 1990-1991 (Box 33)
    - Fuqua Follies, 1989 (Box 33)
    - I.A.T.S.E., 1988 (Box 33)
    - Key re-do, summer1989 (Box 33)
    - Mary Lou Williams Center, 1983 (Box 33)
    - Potty parity and condom machines, 1991-1994 (Box 33)
    - SAFE, 1982-1987 (Box 33)
    - Special Events and Conference Services Operating Board, 1985-1989 (Box 33)
    - Staff meetings, 1993-1994 (Box 33)
    - Student Affairs, 1993-1994; 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Student initiatives, 1993-1994 (Box 33)
    - Student organizations contribution policy, undated (Box 33)
    - University Life--end of year report, 1993-1994; 2 folders (Box 33)
    - Venues and theaters, 1959, 1984-1993, 33 folders (Box 33)
      Variety of materials about the history, specs, andusage policies of Cameron Auditorium, Nelson Music Room, Page Auditorium, Reynolds Theater, Sheafer Theater, and other performing venues at Duke University. Also contains information about various musical instruments on campus, including Duke Chapel's Aeolian and Flentrop organs and the Steinway grand piano used in Page and Reynolds in the 1990s.
  - FY 1994/95: 1958-1995
    - DSG--year end closing, 1995 (Box 33)
    - Duke University Union (DUU), 1958-1995, 7 folders (Box 33)
      Budgets, chairs and officers, endowment and fundraising, and a variety of historical information, possibly gathered for the Union's 40th anniversary in 1995.
    - Hal Kammerer Video Award Application, 1995 (Box 33)
    - On Stage (series), 1994-1995, 4 folders (Box 33)
      Information about the following groups and shows: Alvin Ailey Repertory Ensemble, Connie Clark, "Homecoming Homicide," and Zap Mama.
    - Page Auditorium, 1994-1995, 3 folders (Box 33)
      Acoustics, complaints correspondence, and rental rates.
    - Parents' Weekend, 1995 (Box 33)
    - Speakers: Charles Murray, 1995 (Box 34)
    - Summer housing, 1995 (Box 34)
    - Synergy proposal, 1994-1995 (Box 34)
    - University Life, Office of, 1994-1995, 6 folders (Box 34)
      Agendas and meeting minutes, programming, retreats, year end reports, and other information.
    - WXDU--development, 1994-1995 (Box 34)
  - FY 1995/96: 1990-1996
    - Duke Debate--goals and objectives, 1996 (Box 34)
    - DSG, 1995-1996, 5 folders (Box 34)
      By-laws, constitution, minutes, officers, and funds.
    - DUU, 1990-1996, 11 folders (Box 34)
      Annual report, budget summary, DUU 1995 handbook, and minutes of following committees: Executive, Interaction, Union Board, and Union Development.
    - Event Advising Center (EAC), 1992-1996, 7 folders
      - Banners, 1996 (Box 34)
      - Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 34)
      - David Allan Coe, Widespread Panic, and Carrot Top, 1996 (Box 34)
      - Resources, 1992-1996 (Box 34)
      - Spring retreat, 1996 (Box 34)
      - Staff meetings, 1995-1996 (Box 34)
      - Summer working group, 1996 (Box 34)
      - University privileges, 1996 (Box 34)
    - Kisslo--Reynolds request, 1996 (Box 34)
    - Major Attractions (MA), 1995-1996, 6 folders (Box 34)
      Senior Concert, Mar. 29, 1996: Collective Soul, Drivin' 'n' Cryin', Pharcyde, and The Roots.
    - Major Speakers, 1995-1996, 4 folders (Box 34)
      Committee agendas and minutes; series speaker files for Lisa Jones, Greg Louganis, Alice Walker.
    - Mary Lou Williams Center, 1995-1996 (Box 34)
    - Oktoberfest, 1995 (Box 34)
    - Speakers--various series sponsors, 1996, 2 folders (Box 34)
      Files on Spike Lee, Dinesh D'Souza, and Cornell West.
    - Student Organization Finance Committee (SOFC)--advising and budget, 1995-1996 (Box 34)
    - University Life, Office of, 1990-1996, 8 folders
      - Gift accounts, 1995-1996 (Box 34)
      - Major users--minutes, 1990-1996 (Box 34)
      - Staff meeting agendas, attachments, and minutes, 1995-1996, 2 folders (Box 34)
      - Strategic plan, 1995-1996 (Box 34)
      - Student Affairs Colloquia, 1996 (Box 34)
      - West Union/Bryan Center Task Force, 1995-1996 (Box 34)
      - Year End Report, 1993-1996 (Box 34)
  - FY 1996/97: 1994-1997 (Box 35)
    - DSG--advising, minutes, SOFC, and SOAR Committee, 1996-1997, 4 folders (Box 35)
    - DUU, 1996-1997, 12 folders
      - Annual report, 1996-1997 (Box 35)
      - Budgets, 1996-1997 (Box 35)